(Stuart:)Clearly, you've never seen me
try to talk to a woman.
(Amy:)Guys.
(Bernadette:)In the time you've been sitting
here playing video games,
(Bernadette:)I got the car washed,
picked up cleaning supplies
(Bernadette:)and went to the bank.
(Stuart:)I put on pants.
(Howard:)Kiss-ass.
(Bernadette:)Okay, I don't know when
I became the mother
(Bernadette:)to three lazy teenagers,
(Bernadette:)but it stops today.
(Bernadette:)You guys are cleaning
the kitchen, top to bottom.
(Raj:)Hey, I don't even live here.
(Bernadette:)Yes or no, do you have clothes
in my laundry right now?
(Leonard:)I do.
(Raj:)And some of it's wool,
(Raj:)so dry flat if possible.
(Sheldon:)Oh, and here's a picture
of me receiving
(Sheldon:)my bachelor of science degree.
(Dr Hofstadter:)You don't look
very happy.
(Sheldon:)Well, I had just begun puberty.
(sighs)
(Sheldon:)It was figuratively
and literally
(Sheldon:)one of the hairiest moments
of my life.